DANIELHAMPTON

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER | AUSTIN, TX

Over the past eight years I have made a career of solving problems with technology. Though my primary job responsibilities have mostly been web development, I have always found myself working with various systems and tools and finding creative ways to add value and improve processes. I am currently looking for a job that will present new challenges and provide the opportunity to attempt things that haven't been done before.

EXPERIENCE

SHAREPOINT DEVELOPMENT TEAM LEAD, PHILLIPS 66

JUNE 2013 TO CURRENT

- C#, MVC, ENTITY FRAMEWORK, WEBAPI, JAVASCRIPT, REACT/REDUX, NINJECT/MOQ/NUNIT, POWERSHELL, SQL, REST, JSON, TFS VC
- TECHNICAL LEAD ON SEVERAL LARGE PROJECTS.
- TECH MENTOR FOR NEW EMPLOYEES.
- SOLUTION DESIGN FOR THE SP2013 PLATFORM.
- AGILE PROJECT PLANNING, GATHERING REQUIREMENTS, PRIORITIZING TASKS, COORDINATING TESTING, DELEGATING WORK, DEVELOPING TEAM PROCESSES.

Co-Lead of IT Recruiting for University of Tulsa for Phillips 66May 2012 TO March 2016

- CO-LEAD A TEAM OF 10+ VOLUNTEERS IN RECRUITING EFFORTS FOR THE VARIOUS IT MAJORS AT THE UNIVERSITY OF TULSA FOR JOBS AT PHILLIPS 66.
- BUDGET MANAGEMENT, INTERVIEWING, PRESENTING TO STUDENTS AND FACULTY. PLANNING AND COORDINATING MEETINGS AND EVENTS.

SAP DEVELOPER, PHILLIPS 66/CONOCOPHILLIPS

NOVEMBER 2010 TO JUNE 2013

- ABAP, WEBDYNPRO, ABAP OBJECTS, WINSHUTTLE DEVELOPMENT
 - PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES INCLUDED ABAP DEVELOPMENT AND WINSHUTTLE ADMINISTRATION.
 - PARTICIPATED IN TECHNICAL EFFORTS TO SUPPORT COMPANY SPLIT IN 2012.
- PRIMARY SUPPORT AND TEAM LEAD FOR WINSHUTTLE DEVELOPMENT, SUPPORT, DOCUMENTATION, LICENSE MANAGEMENT, PERMISSIONS, UPGRADES, TRAINING, AND WORKING WITH VENDOR.

REFINING OPERATIONS ANALYST (DEVELOPER), CONOCOPHILLIPS

AUG 2008 TO NOVEMBER 2010

- C#, JAVASCRIPT, SQL, PHP, TFS VC
- WORKED ON AN AGILE PROJECT TEAM THAT DEVELOPED AND IMPLEMENTED A
 CUSTOM WEB APPLICATION BUILT ON TOP OF SHAREPOINT 2007 THAT
 COMBINED DATA FROM VARIOUS REFINERY MONITORING SYSTEMS.
- ENHANCED APPLICATION FUNCTIONALITY AND WROTE IN FUNCTIONALITY TO ALLOW MANY ONE-OFF APPLICATIONS TO BE RETIRED.
- END USER SUPPORT AND TRAINING.

SKILLS

CODING

SOLUTION DESIGN

PROBLEM SOLVING

COMMUNICATION

DOCUMENTATION

LEARNING

MENTORING

PROCESS CREATION

TECHNOLOGIES

C#

JAVASCRIPT

ENTITY FRAMEWORK

WEBAPI

NINIECT/MOO/NUNIT

REACT/REDUX

Powershell

SOL

MVC

REST

ISON

TFS VC

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE MINOR IN MATHEMATICS UNIVERSITY OF TULSA

Tulsa, Oklahoma Graduated May 2008

GPA: 3.8





